["I Got You" by Brophy playing]
♪ I'm just a drifter
in the open ocean ♪
♪ Never knowing
what's underneath ♪
♪ Needing somethin' just
to stop the motion ♪
♪ Slow me down and set me free ♪
♪ Spent your life looking
over your shoulder ♪
♪ Wasting time
Always on the run ♪
♪ Can't seem to get
away from trouble ♪
♪ Fighting back but
it always comes ♪
♪ But you got what I want ♪
♪ And I got what you need... ♪
[man] Happy birthday. Randall!
I was at the cliff.
I missed you.
♪ And we will break
the sky wide open ♪
♪ Ride the river where
the waters meet ♪
♪ We're gonna get to
where we're goin' ♪
♪ 'Cause I got you
and you got me ♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
♪ We're gonna get to
where we're goin' ♪
♪ 'Cause I got you
and you got me ♪
♪ And we will break
the sky wide open ♪
♪ 'Cause I got you
and you got me ♪
♪ We're gonna get to
where we're goin' ♪
♪ 'Now I got you
and you got me ♪
[meat sizzling]
[people chattering]
[chill music playing]
- Cheers.
[gentle music playing]
- I'll catch up with you soon.
- [man 1] Quinn.
- Well. if it isn't Staten Kirkland.
- In the flesh.
- Better late than never.
- [man 2] Quinn.
Staten.
- Davis.
- Great party.
What can I say? I'd do
anything for my nephew.
Look at you. New dress.
- No...
- Brings out the amber flecks in your eyes.
Thank you.
I'll leave you to it. I. uh... I got a
big birthday reveal in the works. so...
[giggles]
- "The amber flecks in your eyes"?
- He was just being nice.
- It's good to see you out off the ranch.
- It's been a while.
That's what the doctor
prescribes after your wife dies.
Two years of heavy sulking. go
all-out shut-in. grow the beard out.
[Quinn] I love it.
Well. I mean. if you like it...
might as well keep it. right?
[girl laughs] Okay.
Hey. hey. hey. hey. Shots
for the birthday boy.
[boy] Ow!
Always looking for trouble.
Baby. I'm not looking for
trouble. I am trouble.
[hushed] Reid. here he comes.
Hey. Uncle Staten.
Hey. boys. Lauren.
Could I get a minute?
- Yeah.
- [Lauren] Mm-hmm.
Thanks.
Where were you this morning?
I waited at the cliff for you.
I never said I was coming.
It's our tradition. Randall.
- [car horn honks]
- [Reid] Randall!
[engine revs]
Hold... Hold...
[pensive music plays]
[Randall] Where are we going?
[Reid] Trust me. trust me.
[Randall laughs]
- No way!
- Yes!
- What?
Uncle Davis!
[Davis] Yeah.
Come on. Dad! I told him
it was your favorite.
[Randall] This is sick.
Most of you knew my sister. I know
right now she's looking down on us.
And she's. uh...
She's saying. "Davey...
you are spoiling that boy."
As I should.
[Randall laughs]
- Happy birthday. Randall.
- Oh my God. Thank you. Uncle Davis.
[guests clapping]
[Davis] Enjoy.
[woman] Let's go.
[Staten] You're gonna
return that car first thing.
People like Davis do not
give gifts without strings.
What've you got against
Uncle Davis anyway?
You act like you're the
only one who lost somebody.
- Okay. I'm warning you...
- You're an asshole.
- That is enough!
- God. I wish it was you that died.
- Randall! Hey! R...
- [door slams]
[phone vibrates]
[Staten groans]
Yeah. hello?
[ominous tone surges]
What are you talking about?
[Staten exhales]
[phone clatters]
[Staten sobbing]
[peaceful music playing]
[woman] Hey. Quinn.
Let's go. Biscuit.
[door closes]
[Biscuit pants. then yips]
Sorry I'm late. Ellie. Tractor
died again. It's a whole thing.
You realize how long it's gonna take me
to sow three acres of lavender by hand?
Well. I hate to pile on. but
the Banjees just canceled.
- But they're playing tonight.
- Not anymore they're not.
[sighs]
How am I supposed to run a dance hall
when the musical acts keep canceling?
Well. I happen to
know a musician.
- [laughing] No.
- Yes.
- No.
- Why not?
We both know the piano I play
isn't the kind people around
here like to dance to.
That and I'm meeting
Staten at the game tonight.
And don't give me that look.
What look?
That look.
Okay. I'm not giving any look.
He's my friend. Ellie.
You and Amalah were friends.
It's not your job to put her
husband's heart back in one piece.
And even if it were. Quinn.
I'm not so sure
you could. I mean.
not after Randall.
[sighs]
[crowd noises swelling]
- [percussion playing]
- [crowd cheering]
Let's go!
Yeah. baby! Let's go!
[marching band
playing lively music]
[woman] Woo-hoo! Spartans!
[girl] Go. Spartans!
- That cherry soda for me?
- [Quinn laughs]
Davis. No. it's not.
[blows raspberry]
- I am wounded. Yeah.
- Are you? Oh.
It's all right. You
can make it up to me.
- Can I?
- Mm. Dinner at Maeve's.
[both laugh]
Not exactly the reaction
I was hoping for.
I'm sorry.
It's just that you've had a
really long time to ask me that.
You've heard of the friend zone?
- Mm-hmm.
- That's right here.
But way up here
- is the brother of the best friend zone.
- Hmm.
That one's real hard to shake off.
In fact. most men don't make it.
You seem to think you have.
Well. you know. Haven't I?
- I don't know.
- Think about it. The offer stands.
- I'm a real good time.
- Oh!
[sentimental music plays]
Hey.
- I feel weird.
- Oh really? Couldn't tell.
[laughing] Oh. piss off.
[Quinn giggles]
- Nachos?
- Oh. thank you.
- Cherry soda?
- Oh!
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- [marching band plays]
[crowd cheering]
[people whooping]I
[crowd cheers and applauds]
[exhales] Okay.
Any sign of that UT scout?
No. no one's ever
gonna come out here.
[romantic music plays]
Lucas Russell's
having a glow-up.
Really? No. I did not notice.
- [percussion plays]
- Okay. guys.
- One on one. Ready!
- [team] Break!
[players grunting]
Come on.
[grunts]
Yes! Yes!
Oh shit! [laughs]
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
[quarterback] Ready! Hut!
[grunting]
[grunts]
[whistle blows]
[melancholy music playing]
Hey.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- Let's get you out of here.
- No. no. no. I'm fine.
I'm good. You stay.
I'm gonna be by tomorrow to
look after that tractor. Okay.
Hut!
[players grunting]
[stirring music playing]
[crowd cheers]
[brakes squeal]
[engine shuts off]
This isn't a good idea.
Lucas. We weren't invited.
Yeah. we're never invited.
It's never a good idea.
Come on. Jack.
["Espresso" by Ryan Oakes plays]
♪ Every single hurdle
they try to fit in ♪
♪ I clear them with a clear
conscience I'm never trippin' ♪
♪ I had a bucket list until it
went and kicked the bucket ♪
♪ I gave it up to move the
needle and it's barely budgin' ♪
♪ It ain't no Biggie rhyme
We can try to up the budget ♪
♪ But every time they pull the
strings I feel like I'm a puppet ♪
♪ You're the
worst Go to work ♪
♪ If you hurt Rub in dirt ♪
♪ Why you mad? ♪
[indecipherable party chatter]
♪ Speed up ♪
♪ Put it first Write a verse ♪
♪ Reimburse ♪
What about "this is over" do you
not understand. Reid Collins?
Babe. you said you wanted
space and I gave you space.
- But it's gone on long enough. okay?
- I know.
I just think we want
different things.
- Hmm.
- Right?
I want something that's...
more than this town.
More isn't always
better. Lauren.
You'll change your mind. You'll
see. You and me are meant to be.
- [Reid laughs]
- [boys shouting]
Ooh. Careful.
That stuff will kill you.
Consider my life saved.
- Means you owe me a blood debt.
- A blood debt?
Is that right?
Now you gotta save me back.
[laughs quietly]
Deal's off.
[lively music playing]
You don't have to tell me this
town is sitting on liquid gold.
I'm the one who pushed the
permits through city hall.
[man] We appreciate
that. Mr. Collins.
but in order to run that
pipeline to the aquifer.
you need to get Staten Kirkland
and Cap Fuller on board.
Without them. the
deal is off the table.
Don't worry. I'll get it done.
That second mortgage on your
ranch is depending on it.
Yeah.
- What are you doing?
- Same thing we've been doing for months.
Yeah. but what if Reid sees?
I can take care of myself.
[Lauren moans]
[soft piano music plays]
[both breathing heavily]
[music continues]
[intriguing music plays]
[vehicle approaches]
[police radio chatter]
[officer] Can I help you. son?
Uh. just heading up to the Fuller
Ranch. Got some work lined up there.
- I'll give you a ride.
- [pats seat]
Come on.
- [car door closes]
- Howdy.
Yancy Grey.
Sheriff Brigman.
Welcome to Ransom Canyon. Yancy.
Where'd you say you
were from again?
You know.
Here and there.
No place special.
I take it you worked
a ranch before?
- Yeah.
- Anywhere I'd know?
Uh...
- It...
- Let me guess.
Here and there.
No place special.
[laughs] Relax. just
busting your chops.
Knowing Cap Fuller. you might want
to head back to here and there.
- Why is that?
- I guess you'll find out.
[animated music playing]
[car door closes]
You're late.
- Sorry about that. Yancy Grey.
- Let's go.
[horse whinnies in distance]
[whinnies]
Now the stalls need mucking.
the horses need shoeing.
fences need mending.
Days are long. and we
already agreed on pay.
That is... well. I don't
renegotiate. you got it?
- I'm your man. Mr. Fuller.
- Your new digs.
[horse snorts]
That a problem?
Feels like home already.
["Color You In" by
Yam Haus playing]
♪ Don't think twice
about what this means ♪
♪ It's just a fantasy
Spinning like rotisserie ♪
♪ When we first caught eyes
I was red in the cheeks ♪
♪ You were a canvas
Standing in front of me ♪
♪ I wanna color you in ♪
Morning to you too. Staten.
[Quinn] Come on. Biscuit.
[light alternative music fades]
[horses whinnying]
Cap?
You in here?
Just who in the hell are you?
- [bangs]
- [Yancy] Ah! Damn!
I think you'll survive.
- Is that your medical opinion?
- Matter of fact. it is.
I used to be a nurse.
Sorry if I... rattled you.
Don't be.
You didn't. You gonna
tell me who you are now?
- Cap's new foreman.
- Oh right!
- Randy.
- Yancy.
And you are?
Ellie Estevez.
Cap and my pops go way back.
so I pop in. keep an eye out.
do some errands for him.
Actually. would you mind
taking this to the house?
Blood pressure meds. I'm
kinda running late for work.
- Hospital?
- Bar.
Well. dance hall.
You should. um. stop by.
"Welcome to Ransom"
drinks on me.
I just might do that.
It's nice to meet
you. Ellie Estevez.
[soft music playing]
Huh.
Look at you.
[foreboding music playing]
What the hell?
[students chattering]
["Blondie" by Modern Aquatic
playing on truck radio]
Hey. thanks for the ride.
- Don't forget. rent is due today.
- Yeah. yeah. I got it handled.
Keep focusing on
school. all right?
[Lucas groans]
Oh!
- And stay out of trouble. Kit.
- Mm.
♪ And you You try ♪
♪ To work your way back
in to see my life ♪
[laughs] Way to
shoot your shot. bro.
- [class bell rings]
- [upbeat alternative music stops]
- Guess what?
- What?
[laughs] Turns out UT's scout
was at the game after all.
Shut up.
She wants us to come to
Austin for their cheer clinic.
- You know what this could mean?
- It could mean a full ride to UT!
- That's right. We did it. bitch.
- We did it. yeah!
[laughing and screaming]
[Quinn] Oh.
- Would you like some pie?
- Hm.
- Needs a new belt. doesn't it?
- Yep.
- Did I not say it was the belt?
- You did.
And you were right.
Sorry about last night.
Shouldn't have pushed you to go.
No. you didn't... You
didn't push. It's fine.
I just... I guess
I just wanted...
Wanted to what?
What. ease me back into
the world of the living?
Yeah.
I get it.
Oh. I can do that.
Already done.
[water shuts off]
[quiet. emotional music playing]
You used to wear your hair
like that in high school.
Yeah.
Okay. well. I'll figure that belt
out and get back to you tomorrow.
All right.
Yeah. okay. I'll see you then.
[footsteps receding]
[vehicle approaching]
[engine shuts off]
[truck door closes]
I'm gonna need a drink for this.
[Staten exhales]
- [bottle top clinks]
- So...
To what do I owe
the pleasure. Davis?
You're really gonna
make me say it?
Well. I know it's not because you want me
to sell my land to those Austin water boys
so they can build their
damn pipeline. right?
This is my home.
I know.
And it will stay that way.
They'll guarantee a leaseback.
Nothing changes.
Except you. me. and Cap will all
be. uh. several million richer.
Yeah. I don't need
any more money.
[laughing] Yeah.
I know you don't.
But. you know. you inherited
60.000 acres in a trust fund. so...
[laughs] Yeah. well. you're not
doing so bad yourself. are you?
[exhales]
Staten...
This would be good for
Ransom. for the town.
Look. don't be so provincial. Think about
people apart from yourself for once.
You got no goddamn sense.
The world's drying up.
That aquifer feeds our wells.
our crops. and our cattle.
and I'm not gonna let them
run it dry. You understand?
[tense music playing]
Staten. the town has already
granted permission for the pipeline.
It's only a matter of
time until I find a way.
with or without you.
Thanks for the drink.
[distant birds calling]
[horse squealing]
[whinnying]
[snorts]
[Staten whispers] Hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
it's okay. it's okay.
Hey. it's all right.
It's all right.
You gotta be patient. all right?
Breaking a horse takes time.
All right. Come on.
It's okay. It's okay.
Ready. boss?
[wind blowing]
[sighs]
[solemn music playing]
[sniffles]
[quietly sobbing]
[mysterious music playing]
[Jake] What you
got there. Staten?
An answer.
Who the hell's that?
Looks like Austin Water & Power
surveying for the pipeline again.
God damn it.
All right. you tell them that
this is private property.
If they don't leave. you shoot 'em.
Kidding. Just... Just get rid of 'em.
[Staten] There it is.
There's your proof.
Proof of what exactly?
Proof there was another
car on the road that night.
[sighs]
Dan. I'm... Listen.
I'm telling you.
Somebody else made him crash.
Look. I know this is hard.
today being a year and all.
But your boy was alone out there
that night. You understand?
You gotta let this theory go.
Staten...
Hey. [sighs] Have you
thought about taking a break?
Maybe giving yourself
a little vacation?
Well. I'm just saying it
might do you some good.
Might... Might do me some good?
You know what would do me some good.
Dan. is if you did your goddamn job.
[footsteps receding]
Why do you let him talk
to you like that. Sheriff?
Well. because that man has
lost everything he loves. Kai.
And he's looking for a reason.
Even if there isn't one.
[pensive music playing]
[mechanical creaking]
[machinery clicking
and creaking]
- [creaking]
- [Staten grunts]
[creaking continues]
- [mechanism bangs]
- [Staten exclaims]
[frustrated groan]
[Quinn] Want me to get in there?
Smaller hands.
No. I'll get it.
[ratchet clicking]
[Staten panting]
[grunts]
Hey.
Talk to me.
I'm good.
[continues ratcheting]
Would you just let
me fix the damn belt?
Yeah. you know what?
Have at it. Staten.
[pensive music plays]
[class bell rings]
[Lauren] My mom's a drunk. and
I'm the one who has to stay.
Oh come on. Your dad wouldn't make
you give up a full ride at UT.
Well. he did.
He doesn't realize being stuck here
is what made my mom the way she is.
I just don't want
to end up like her.
I won't.
Hey.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
[serious music playing]
[horse whinnies]
Not gonna use the power sander?
- You got a power sander?
- Yup.
Might have been. uh. helpful to
let me know before I started.
Well. I'm not one
to micromanage.
[vehicle approaching]
[truck door opens]
[door closes]
Don't get up.
I know how hard that
is for you these days.
[Cap groans]
Couple years ago. I'd have
whooped your ass bad for that.
- Think we both know you still could.
- You want a beer?
No. no. I'm set. How
you doing. old boy?
Eh.
You... getting
charitable over here?
We'll see how long he lasts.
What's eating at you?
[sighs]
- Austin Water & Power.
- Oh.
They been dripping
honey in your ear too?
They're trying to.
Davis came by. wants me
to sit down with 'em.
I think we need to
lock arms on this. Cap.
Let me talk to the utilities commission
and have them run some oversight.
The numbers they're batting
around ain't nothing.
Yeah. I know the
numbers. all right?
But these are our homes
we're talking about.
These ranches are our legacy.
Legacy to who?
Our sons are dead.
[muffled music playing]
What can I get you?
Shiner'd be nice.
- [aggressive thud]
- [bottlecap clatters]
Did I miss something here?
I saw that article
in your little book.
I care about Cap.
You could work at half a dozen
ranches for twice the pay.
It just didn't make any
sense. And then I...
And then you thought
the worst. I get it.
Look. far as other ranches are concerned.
the last place I was at didn't go so well.
Cap was the only one that
didn't ask for references.
As far as that paper.
I was just trying to see
what his place used to be.
see if I could
help bring it back.
And that's it?
That's it.
You so much as cross
that old man...
I will see to it you suffer.
Yes. ma'am.
[rap music playing]
♪ Bad energy don't
suit the fella ♪
♪ Dunno why I keep that fruit ♪
♪ Better calm down They
super jealous. over-zealous ♪
Cheers!
♪ We celebrate for the hell
of it. got champagne pop... ♪
Yo. uh. Lucas.
When are you gonna come
work for my dad. man?
- What?
- I mean. like. your brother's there now.
You know. your old man
was there back in the day.
Just a regular Russell
family tradition.
Yeah. I guess so.
Your dad taught me how
to ride when I was a kid.
- I didn't know that.
- He was a hell of a wrangler too.
That he was.
[music continues]
Hey.
- What are y'all doing up here?
- [Reid] You're just in time.
I was about to clear
something up with Lucas here.
You need to leave
my woman alone.
- Oh my God.
- [Lucas] Uh...
I'm sorry. I think I'm mistaken.
Do we have a problem here?
You gotta be kidding me with
this toxic male whatever this is.
Really? Lucas. let's go.
Come on.
[ominous music plays]
- [police siren blares]
- [boy] Cops!
Yo. check it out. check it out!
- [teens clamoring]
- [boy] No. no!
[car engines revving. leaving]
Oh God. Did any
of you guys drive?
- No.
- Ben was designated.
I don't have a car.
Great.
Okay. well...
Yeah. we have no service
either. so we're stranded.
[Lauren sighs]
- Whoa.
- Hey. how is this my fault?
- [Lauren] Let's go.
- [Reid] What'd I do?
You were not at that show.
Rampart Theater. back
row. I swear to God.
[laughs] You are full of it.
[laughs] Okay. listen.
I was at school.
Amalah told me that you
had a showcase concert.
Mm-hmm.
So I went into the city
and I. uh. saw you play.
You were... You
were unbelievable.
[laughs]
Okay. in case it hasn't
been abundantly clear.
I've had a thing for you
since... since forever.
Look. I... I was always
worried that you. um...
You know. you wouldn't
see me as anything more
than your best friend's little brother
who was utterly infatuated with you.
And yet you've been utterly
infatuated before. Mr. Collins.
I was at your wedding.
- [laughs]
- Both of them.
Whatever happened to Miss Texas?
- It's complicated.
- Ah. okay.
So... [clears throat]
Why didn't you go back?
When Amalah got sick and
you came home from New York?
Why didn't you go back?
[door opens]
It's complicated.
[door closes]
[footsteps approach]
[Staten] Hey. June.
I'm here to pick up.
[June] Coming right up.
Thank you.
Tell your buddies at Austin
Water & Power to stop calling.
because I'm not
selling. You understand?
Yeah. uh. sorry about that.
[apprehensive music playing]
Well...
[somber music plays]
[thunder rumbles]
What the hell is she
doing with Davis?
Oh my God.
[Lauren] Please. be quiet!
[Lucas] Oh hey! Hey!
[all] Hey!
And the Darwin Award goes to...
[thunder crashing]
All right. There. Let's
take cover over there.
Ghost house? No way. man.
Fine. Freeze.
[wind blowing]
[frustrated growl]
[thunder continues]
[door slams]
- [thunder crashes]
- [Lauren gasps]
[Lauren] Guys...
Reid. I don't have a
good feeling about this.
[floor creaks. snaps]
This floor isn't stable.
[floorboard creaks]
Hey. stop.
- It's gonna be fine.
- [Tim] Don't. man.
- What?
- [Lauren] Reid. stop.
- Reid. no!
- [crashing]
[Lucas and Reid yell]
- [Lauren gasps]
- Oh God.
- Over there!
- [boy] My leg!
[boy groans]
[floorboards crumbling]
[Lucas] Lauren. come on.
[thunder rumbles]
Lauren?
[panicked breathing]
- [boy moans]
- [floorboards crumble]
Look at me. Walk to me.
I can't move. I can't move.
[clattering]
Don't... Don't let me fall.
[Lucas] I won't.
[Lauren gasping]
I've got you.
I got you. Come on.
[grunting]
Tim?
Tim!
Oh God.
[grunting]
[panting. groaning]
[Staten] Come on.
Ah!
[Staten] You guys stay put.
Sheriff's on his way.
[Tim groans]
[police radio chattering]
[Reid] Look. all right. I could
tell the floor was unsafe.
And I tried to get 'em to stop
horsing around over there.
They didn't. And then
the floor gave out.
Nuh-uh.
- No. I'm gonna tell him the truth.
- Let's let him play the hero.
But. Lucas. this is
just wrong. Like...
You know the truth.
That's all that matters to me.
[vehicle approaching]
[whispers] Is that your dad?
- [door opens and closes]
- Oh shit!
Dad. listen. I'm fine. okay?
Give me a minute to explain...
Not right now.
I'm still mentally composing the lecture
I'm gonna be giving you the next 10 years.
- Let's go.
- [dispatcher] 3-1. what's your 20?
Sarge. this is 4-9 Charlie...
I'm gonna say this
once and only once.
You stay away from that boy.
- That Russell family is trouble.
- But. Dad. you don't understand...
It's not up for discussion.
Now. I am willing to
reconsider that cheer clinic.
at least for now. but this...
this is my one condition.
[somber music playing]
- Hey. Don't worry. Your nephew's okay.
- What happened?
Ah. he's banged up.
Broken legs and busted ribs.
but he's gonna be fine.
Your sister's in there now.
Thank you.
So. Davis. huh?
Now's not really the best time.
All right.
You're unbelievable.
you know that?
You've had a piece of my heart
for as long as I can remember.
- Hold on. What are...
- Listen.
I buried it when you and
Amalah started dating.
Buried it even more when
you two got married.
I moved halfway across
the country to avoid it.
["Hold Me Steady"
by Ronen playing]
When she got sick. I was
here for her and you.
And I've been here ever
since. through all of it.
Through the pain.
the grief.
Through Randall.
And I've waited.
I've waited for you to heal...
to choose me.
But you're never gonna
do that. are you?
Quinn. I...
Why do you care what I do?
I don't.
♪ Hold me steady It's
all so heavy sometimes ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Hold me steady ♪
Damn it.
[gentle piano music fades]
[lighter flicks]
- [vehicle approaches]
- [lighter shuts]
All's going to plan with Cap.
But you didn't tell
me about the girl.
[soft. dramatic music playing]
Does it matter?
We're sure about this?
'Cause once you go through
with it. there's no going back.
That's what I'm counting on.
[soft. pensive music playing]
[music fades]
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-